Who the winny-binny boy?
我的小不点儿
You the winny-winny-binny-binny boy!
你是个小小的小不点儿
Don't cry.
不要哭啊
不要哭嘛
Why is he still crying?
他为什么还在哭？
Let me hold him for a sec.
我来抱他一下
Here we go.
来，爸爸抱
There we are.
不哭了
Maybe it's me.
或许是因为我
Don't be silly. Ben loves you. He's just being Mr. Cranky Pants.
别傻了，班爱你 他只是爱发牢骚而已
You know,I once dated a Miss Cranky Pants.
我跟一个牢骚小姐约过会呀
Lovely girl. IKind of moody.
好女孩，有点情绪化就是了
There we go,all better.
好了，好多了
There's my little boy.
这才是小乖乖
Can I see something?
我可以试一件事吗？
Cool!
酷哎
He hates me. My nephew hates me!
他恨我，我的┳雍尬
Come on,don't do this.
好啦，不要这样嘛
What if my own baby hates me? What do I do then?
要是我自己孩子恨我 怎么办啊？
Monica,stop! This is nuts.
摩妮卡，你住口好不好？ 你疯了是不是啊？
Do you know how long it'll be before you have to deal with this?
你知道你还要多久 才会遇到这个问题呢？
You don't even have a boyfriend yet.
我是说你现在连男朋友都没有
Joey,she does not look fat.
乔伊，她看起来不胖
The One With the Baby on the Bus
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第06集 宝宝落在巴士上了
Here you go.
拿去
Goo,goo,goo!
咕，咕，咕！
That is so funny! Let me see that a sec.
真好笑，那个借我一下
You okay?
你还好吧，罗斯？
I don't know.
不知道
What's in this pie?
馅饼里有什么呀？
I don't know. Butter and eggs and flour and lime and kiwi
不知道，奶油，鸡蛋，面粉 莱姆，奇异果跟…
Kiwi? Kiwi?!
奇异果？奇异果？
You said it was a key lime pie.
你说这个是奇莱馅饼
No,I didn't. I said kiwi lime. That's what makes it so special.
不是，我是说奇异果莱姆 所以才会那么特别
That's what's gonna kill me.
所以我才会死
I'm allergic to kiwi.
我对奇异果过敏
No,you're not. You're allergic to lobster and peanuts and
你才不会呢 你会过敏的是龙虾，花生跟…
Oh,my God!
天啊
It's definitely getting worse.
越来越严重了
Is your tongue swelling up?
你的舌头肿了吗？
Either that or my mouth is getting smaller!
要不然就是我的嘴小了
Get your coat. We're going to the hospital.
穿外套，我们现在就到医院去
-Will he be okay? -He's gotta get a shot.
他不会怎么样吧？ 不会，只是得打一针
You know,actually, it's getting better. It is.
事实上我觉得好多了
Let's not go. Anyone up for Scrabble?
没错，别去了 谁要玩拼字游戏啊？
Jacket,now!
去穿外套
What about Ben? We can't bring a baby to the hospital.
但是班怎么办呢？ 我们不能带个宝宝去医院啊
We'll watch him.
交给我们吧
I don't think so.
恕难从命
I have seven Catholic sisters. I've taken care of hundreds of kids.
干嘛？我有七个天主教姐妹 我照顾过上百个小孩
Come on,we want to do it. Don't we?
别这样 我们想帮忙，对不对？
I was gonna play basketball...
拜托，我本来想去打篮球的…
... but I guess that's out the window.
…不过球被丢出窗外去了
If you take him out for a walk, remember to bring his hat.
好，如果你要带他去散步 记得要帮他戴帽子，好吗？
There's milk in the refrigerator and diapers in the bag.
冰箱里还有一些牛奶 尿布在袋子里
Hat,milk....
帽子，牛奶…
Got it!
懂了
Consider it done!
包在我身上啊
You understood?
你听得懂吗？
My uncle Sal has a really big tongue.
懂啊，我沙叔叔就有大舌头
Is he the one with the beautiful wife?
他是老婆很正的那个
中央公园
You want to hear the song I'm singing this afternoon?
阿秋，要不要听听 我今天下午要唱的新歌呢？
I wrote it this morning in the shower.
今天早上洗澡的时候写的
I'm in the shower And I'm writing a song
我一边洗澡一边在写歌
Stop me if you've heard it
听过的话请阻止我
My skin is soapy and my hair is wet
我全身泡沫，头发湿搭搭
And Tegrin spelled backward is nirget
香皂倒过来是皂香
Rachel,sweetheart, could I see you for a minute?
瑞秋，亲爱的 麻烦你过来一下好吗？
What's up?
什么事啊？
FYK:
告诉你…
I've decided to pay a professional musician to play here on Sundays.
我决定以后周日的下午 要付钱请一位职业歌手来演出
Her name is Stephanie something. She's supposed to be very good.
她叫什么芬妮的，很出色的
But what about Phoebe?
但菲比怎么办？
It's not that your friend is bad.
瑞秋，你的朋友不是差而已
It's that she's so bad...
她实在是差到…
...she makes me want to put my finger through my eye into my brain...
差到让我想把手指头 伸进我的眼睛里
...and swirl it around.
然后把脑袋搅成浆糊
Okay,so you're not a fan.
那好，你不是她的歌迷
But,I mean,come on. You cannot do this to her.
可是你不能这样对她嘛
I have to do this to her?
你叫我出面？
Lather,rinse,repeat
涂皂，冲水，再一次…
And lather,rinse,repeat
As needed
视需要而定
We didn't bring enough stuff.
我觉得我们东西没有带够
Did you forget to pack the baby's anvil?
你有没有记得 把宝宝的止痛药带出来？
I'm telling you,it'll be worth it.
我告诉你，这绝对值得
It's a known fact that women love babies.
大家都知道女人最爱宝宝了
Women love guys who love babies. It's the sensitive thing.
女人爱喜欢宝宝的男人 这是感性的问题，懂了吗？
Aim him at that pack of babes. Maybe one of them will break away.
把他对准那边那些宝贝 说不定待会儿有一个会过来
Wait,forget them. We got one. Hard left.
不…等一下 算了，正左方
-Give me the baby. -No,I got him.
来，宝宝给我 不要，我要抱
Come on,seriously.
快，我说真的
Oh,seriously,you want him?
你真的要他吗？
Who is this little cutie-pie?
这个小可爱是谁啊？
Well,don't think me immodest,but...
不要怪我不懂得谦虚，但…
... me.
…我
Want to smell him?
要不要嗅嗅他？
I assume we're talking about the baby?
我想你指的是宝宝吧？
He's got that great baby smell. Get a whiff of his head.
是呀，他的宝宝味好香 嗅嗅他的头
My uterus just skipped a beat.
我想我的子宫刚刚顿了一下
What'd I tell you?
你看吧
It's great you're doing this.
我觉得你们这样做很棒
Well,we are great guys.
我们都是很棒的男人
My brother and his boyfriend have been trying to adopt.
我弟弟跟他的男友 试了三年都领养不到孩子
What agency did you two go through?
你们是找哪一家办的？
But this is my gig.
这是我的表演
This is where I play.
这是我的地盘
My name is written out there in chalk.
我的名字用粉笔写在外面
You know,you can't just erase chalk.
你不能把粉笔擦掉的
Honey,I'm sorry.
对不起，我很遗撼
And he's going to be paying this woman?
而且他居然还要付这个女人钱
Why doesn't he just give her a throne and a crown?
那他干脆给她一个宝座 一顶皇冠
And,like,a gold stick with a ball on top?
还有一根上面有球的权杖
Terry is a jerk! That's why we always say,"Terry's a jerk!"
泰利是混蛋，所以我们才会 常说“泰利是混蛋”
That's where that came from.
不然我们干嘛那么说
You probably did everything you could.
你说不定已经尽力了
You know what? Let me just see what else I could do.
好吧，这样让我看看 还有没有别的办法
Just let her go on after Stephanie whatever her name is.
你何不让她接在 那个叫黛什么芬的后面唱啊？
You won't be here. You don't pay her.
你又不在这里，又不付她钱
I don't know.
我不知道
I'll clean the cappuccino machine!
我帮你洗卡布基诺机好了
You don't clean the cappuccino machine?
你不洗卡布基诺机吗？
Of course I clean it.
我当然会
I mean,I will clean it.
我是说我会清洗
我会清的
All right,fine,fine,fine!
好…
-Done. -Really?
成了 真的？
Who's working for you,babe?
对呀，看谁出马嘛
Oh,my God! This is so exciting! How much am I gonna get?
天啊，好兴奋哦 我会收到多少钱啊？
What?
什么？
He's paying the people who were playing.
你说他要付钱给演出的人
I meant,he's paying that other woman because she's a professional.
我是说他要付另外那个女人钱 因为她是职业歌手
I'm not gonna be the only one who's not getting paid.
我可不想当那个 唯一没有收到钱的人
I'm sorry,no!
对不起，不
No,I'm not some sloppy second, you know,charity band.
不，我可不是什么二流的… 慈善乐团
There are thousands of places in this city...
这个城市里面有上千个地方…
...where people would pay to hear me play.
…愿意付钱听我来演唱
When I play,I play for me
我为自己而演唱
I don't need your charity
我不需要你的施舍
Thank you!
谢谢
I'm not getting a shot. Maybe they can take the needle...
你说什么都别想叫我打针 我是说，或许他们可以把…
...and squirt it into my mouth. Like a squirt gun.
…药水射进我的嘴里 就像水枪那样
Hello there. I'm Dr. Carlin.
你们好，我是林医生
I see someone's having a little allergic reaction.
好像有人有一点点过敏的反应
Doctor,can I see you for just a moment?
对，医生 我可以单独跟你谈谈吗？
My brother has a slight phobia about needles.
我哥哥有一点点害怕打针
Did you tell him about my squirt gun idea?
你有没有告诉他 我那个水枪的主意？
My brother,the Ph.D., would like to know...
我的博士哥哥想知道…
...if there's any way to treat this orally?
这个药有没有可能用口服的？
Under these circumstances,it has to be an injection,and it has to be now.
在这种情况之下，打针是 避免不了的，而且要马上打针
So?
怎么样？
Go and have a seat. The doctor says it's got to be a needle.
好吧，坐下来 医生说这一针非打不可
You're just going to have to be brave. Can you do that for me?
所以你一定要勇敢起来 为我这么做，好不好？
Oh,boy! You are doing so good.
你做得非常好
You want to squeeze my hand?
要不要握紧我的手啊？
Ross,don't squeeze it so hard.
罗斯，不要握得那么紧
Honey,really. Don't squeeze it so hard!
真的，不要握那么紧
Let go of my hand!
罗斯，放开我的手
Good plan. Next time we want to pick up women...
还真是个好计划 下一回想泡妞…
...we should go to the park and make out.
…我们干脆直接去公园 亲热算了
Taxi! Taxi!
计程车…
Look at that talent.
你看那票妞儿
Just practicing. You're good.
只是在练习，你很行
Carry on.
继续开吧
Wait,wait,wait!
等等，等等我们
Hey,you. He's just adorable.
他好可爱哦
Can you tell him that? Because he thinks he looks too pink.
告诉他，好不好？ 他觉得他脸色太红润了
-What are you guys out doing today? -We're not out.
你们今天出来做什么？ 我们没有
We're two heterosexual guys hanging with the son...
我们只是帮我们的 异性恋朋友…
...of our other heterosexual friend, doing the usual straight-guy stuff.
…带孩子的异性恋男人 做一般男人应该做的事情
You done?
讲完了？
There's our stop.
我们到了
Get out of here! This is our stop.
少来了，我们才到了
You guys live around here too?
你们也住在这附近啊？
We live in the building by the sidewalk.
我们住在那个人行道旁边
You know it?
你们知道吗？
Since we're neighbors,what do you say we get together for a drink?
对了，既然大家是邻居嘛 我们聚一聚喝点东西，如何？
So you want to go to Markel's?
我们去马可咖啡厅，好吗？
Sure,they love us over there.
好啊，他们很喜欢我们
Where's your baby?
你们的宝宝呢？
Ben! Ben!
班…
That's good. Maybe he'll hear you and pull the cord!
或许他会听到拉铃啊
Stop the bus!
停车
Are you sure he didn't break it? It hurts.
你肯定没有捏断？我真的很痛
No,it's just a good bone bruise.
没有，只是有一块瘀青
And right here is the puncture wound from your ring.
还有这是你戒指压出来的痕迹
-I'm really sorry. -It's okay.
对不起，我真的很抱歉 没关系
Sorry.
抱歉…
Sorry! I got my S's back!
抱歉…我说清楚了
Which we can celebrate later.
那我们待会儿再庆祝
Celebrate. Celebrate....
庆祝…
He was a double,double
他是个双双双
Double-jointed boy
双关节男孩
So are you the professional guitar player?
你就是那个专业的吉他手吗？
Yeah,I'm Stephanie.
对，我叫黛芬
Right. My name was on there, but now it just says carrot cake.
对，上面本来有我名字的 现在只剩红萝N糕了
So how many chords do you know?
你会弹几个和弦？
-All of them. -So you know D?
全都会啊 是吗？那你会D调
Do you know A-minor?
那你会A小调吗？
Do you know how to go from D to A-minor?
你会从D和弦转到A小调吗？
So does your guitar have a strap?
那你的吉他有背带吗？
Mine does.
我的有
Stephanie knows all the chords
黛芬什么和弦都会
Come on! Pick up,pick up!
快接…
Transit Authority?
运输中心吗？
I'm doing research for a book.
我在帮一本书做调查
I was wondering what somebody might do if they left a baby on a city bus.
如果有人把婴儿留在市公车上 那该怎么办呢？
Yes,I realize that would be a stupid character.
是，我知道 只有笨蛋才会这么做
Here's the deal: We lost a car seat on a bus.
我们今天在公车上 掉了汽车安全座椅
It's white plastic and it fits onto a stroller.
白塑胶材质 有把手，可以用在推车上面
And there was a baby in it.
里面还有一个婴儿
He wants to talk to you.
他要跟你讲
Everybody,let's give a warm Central Perk welcome to
各位 我们以最热烈的掌声欢迎…
Terry's a jerk And he won't let me work
泰利是个混蛋 他不让我工作
And I hate Central Perk
我恨中央咖啡园
To Stephanie Schiffer!
欢迎史黛芬
I'd like to start with a song I wrote for the first man I ever loved.
首先我想唱一首 我为我的初恋情人写的歌
Zachary
柴克力…
Are all invited to bite me
被邀来咬我
We're the guys that called about the baby! Is he here?!
我们打过电话来公车上的婴儿 怎么样了？到了没有…
He's here.
到了
I assume one of you is the father.
你们之中有一个是父亲吧
-That's me. -I'm him.
是我 是我
Actually,we're both the father.
事实上呢，我们两个都是
Oh,Ben! Hey,buddy.
宝贝…
Please tell me you know which one is our baby.
你知道哪个是班吗？
That one has ducks on his T-shirt and this one has clowns.
那个T恤上有鸭子 这个有小丑
And Ben was definitely wearing ducks.
班绝对是穿着鸭子T恤的
Or clowns.
或小丑
That one's Ben! Remember he had that cute little mole by his mouth!
等一下，那个绝对是班 记得他嘴边那颗可爱的小痣
Hey,Ben! Remember us?
班，记得我们吗？
Okay,the mole came off.
天啊，痣掉了
What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办？
We'll flip for it. Ducks or clowns.
丢铜板决定，鸭或小丑
-Flip for the baby? -You got a better idea?
要丢铜板决定 你有更好的主意吗？
All right,call it in the air.
好吧，在空中叫
Heads.
头
Heads,it is.
就是头
We have to assign heads to something!
我们得决定头是哪一个
Right!
好的！
Ducks is heads because ducks have heads.
鸭子是头，因为鸭子有头
What kind of scary-ass clowns came to your birthday?
帮你庆祝生日的小丑没有头 不会吓坏你吗？
Just call me angel Of the morning,angel
叫我清晨天使
Just touch my cheek Before you leave me,baby
在离开我之前 轻触我的脸颊
Just call me angel Of the morning,angel
叫我清晨天使
Then slowly turn away
然后转身离去
I won't beg you to stay
我不会求你留下来
With me
陪我
Here. I thought you might be cold.
来，我想你可能会冷
Thank you.
谢谢
Look at you! You did pretty well.
看看你，干得不错嘛
$8. 27.
这里一共是八块又二十七分
But not really,because I put in the first two.
其实没那么多啦 头两块是我放的
Just to get the ball rolling and to make myself feel better.
只是让钱滚滚来 还有让自己舒服一点
Do you?
结果呢？
You know,this whole playing for money thing is so not good for me.
为了钱演奏这码子事 对我非常的不好
I don't know,when l sang "Su-su-suicide"...
我不知道 当我唱到“自杀”…
... I got,like,$ 1. 75.
…我得到一块七十五分钱
But then "Smelly Cat"?
可是“臭臭猫”呢？
I got 25 cents and a condom.
二十五分钱跟一个保险套
So,you know,now I just feel really bad for "Smelly Cat."
所以现在我为“臭臭猫” 感到很难过
Honey,I don't think everybody gets "Smelly Cat."
我不认为 大家都会懂“臭臭猫”啊
I mean,if all you've ever actually had are healthy pets,then whoosh!
我是说 如果你只要养过健康的猫的话
But it's not even that,you know?
可是根本就不是那个嘛
I used to do my songs because it made me happy.
本来我唱歌只是因为我很高兴
Now it's just all about the money,you know?
可是现在却变成全都是为了钱
Well,people missed you in there.
菲比，大家都很想你
In fact,there was actually a request for "Smelly Cat."
事实上 还有人指名要听“臭臭猫”呢
Really? From who?
真的啊？是谁呢？
Well,me.
我啊，就是我
And I know it's not your big money song,but it's my favorite.
我知道那不是赚大钱的歌 但我最喜欢的就是那首
Did I accidentally drop a condom in your case?
我是不是 不小心丢了一个保险套啊？
It's kind of an emergency.
情况紧急嘛
-Here you go. -Thanks a lot.
拿去吧 谢了
Hey,Christine! I got it!
克丽丝，拿到了
I want to thank you for being there for me.
我只是想要谢谢你今天的帮忙
And I'm sorry I almost broke your hand.
对不起，我差点捏断你的手
That's okay. I'm sorry I poisoned you.
没关系，抱歉你中了我的毒
Remember the time I jammed that pencil into your hand?
你还记得 我用铅笔戳你的手那回吗？
Remember it? What do you think this is,a freckle?
记得吗？ 你以为这是什么？雀斑啊
What about the time I hit you in the face with Sylvian's pumpkin?
等等，那我用薇恩的南瓜 打你脸那一次呢？
Remember when I stuck that broom in your spokes...
天啊，记得我把扫把 插进你脚踏车轮里…
...and you hit your head on the curb?
结果你翻车头撞到路边那次吗
But I remember people telling me about it.
不，我记得 是别人告诉我那件事
I hope Ben has a little sister.
我希望班有个小妹妹
And I hope she can kick his ass.
希望她能够好好的整整他
I'm gonna get a new Band-Aid.
我去拿一个新的绷带
How about the time I cut the legs off your Malibu Ken?
我切下 你马里布肯娃娃的腿那次呢？
That was you?
是你干的啊？
They were infected. He wouldn't have made it.
对，它的腿发炎了 不切的话它会死
My little nephew.
我的小┳
Come here,little one!
过来，小东西
There's my little baby,Ben!
我的小宝贝班班
Hey,he's not crying!
他居然没有哭
他没哭呀
There's still pie!
还有馅饼
I'm here. I'm here.
我在，我在
How's my little boy?
我的小宝贝好吗？
You want Daddy to change your diaper? I know,I know.
要爸爸帮你换尿布，对不对？ 我知道…
Did you have fun with Uncle Joey and Uncle Chandler today?
你今天跟乔伊叔叔 还有钱德叔叔玩得开心吗？
He rode the bus today.
开心，他今天坐公车了
Big boy riding the bus
好耶，大男生坐公车喔
Hey,I have a question.
我有个问题耶
How come it says, "Property of Human Services"?
他的小屁股上为什么会有 “服务处财产”这些字？
You are gonna love this.
你一定会觉得很精采的
Can you hold Ben for a sec?
帮我抱一下班，好吗？
Come here. Come here.
过来…
Stay back! I've got kiwi! Run,Joey,run!
别过来，我有奇异果 跑呀，乔伊
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫…
What are they feeding you?
你都吃些什么啊？
No,no. I'm sorry,it's:
不对…对不起
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫…
Better!
好一点了
Much better. Good.
好多了
Don't feel bad, because it's a hard song.
你知道吗？不要难过 这首歌本来就很难
-You want to try it again? -From the top?
要不要再试一次？ 好，从头
There is no "top," all right?
这次没有头，好吗？
That's the beauty of "Smelly Cat."
那是“臭臭猫”的美妙之处
Why don't you just follow me.
你跟着我唱好了 好
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫…
What are they feeding you?
他们喂你什么？
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
It's not your fault
不是你的错
That's too much. Sorry.
太夸张了，对不起